http://www.braindumps.biz/privacy.php

Explore
Purchase all exams?
Privacy Policy
HotCerts respects your privacy. From our business, around the world, we will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to offer help and keep a good relationship with you, for example, to process your order, provide service and support, and send you new release products or any update news, we will never sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside the HotCerts family of companies with your consent, as required by law or to protect HotCerts, its customers, or the public, or with companies that help HotCerts fulfill its obligations with you, and then only with partners who share HotCerts's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. At any time you may contact HotCerts with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes.
Privacy and Data Security
At HotCerts, your right to privacy and data security is a very important. That's why, when you visit HotCerts.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet site or when you use our online support offerings such as FAQs.HotCerts.com.
HotCerts only requests for specific information used in our product or service
In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with purchase and technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate. For example, we request information from you when you:
Register a new user on HotCerts.com
Request a quote for some products
Place an order
Provide feedback in an online survey
Request e-mail notification of your order status
Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list
Request assistance from our "Livesupport!"
Information we may request includes your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, company name, customer preference information, order number, as well as other similar personal information. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you.
HotCerts only uses your personal information for specific purposes
The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with HotCerts. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on HotCerts.com and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from HotCerts. Agents or contractors of HotCerts who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for HotCerts. HotCerts may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you. In addition, HotCerts may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if HotCerts reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect HotCerts, its customers, or the public.
HotCerts will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent.
To view or edit the information that has been stored online, please visit the My Account of the HotCerts Web site.
Internet Commerce
The online store at HotCerts.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. HotCerts is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called SSL encryption, at our payment gateways. It has always been a HotCerts practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase.
Customized Experience
We use technology to help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At HotCerts, we primarily use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine and to maintain your shopping experience in our online store. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. We might be able to ascertain what type of computer you are using, but beyond that, our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using www.HotCerts.com. HotCerts has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the HotCerts.com site. For more information about our use of cookies, please click here.
Changes to the Policy
We reserve the right to change the terms, conditions, notices and privacy under which this website is offered without notice at any time.
Contact HotCerts
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please write us at the following email address: legal@HotCerts.com
Exams | Guarantee | FAQ | Contact Us | Samples | Terms & Conditions | Privacy
Copyright @ Braindumps.biz Pvt Ltd
